# **HENRY CHEN**

Ln. 435, Sec. 3, Heping E. Rd., Xinyi Dist., Taipei City M: +886952890993 holyman1010@gmail.com https://goo.gl/A6k0PL

#### **Profile**

User-centered product designer with over 8 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing digital design strategies. Innovative use of technology and CRO to drive user experience and achieve business goal. Be good at coordinate cross-function to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with intuitive, user-friendly designs.

## **Areas of Expertise**

- Conversion rate optimization
- Strong collaborative skills
- User interface design skills
- Front-end programming skills
- Project management
- User research and interview skills
- Digital marketing analytics and optimization
- Excellent problem-solving skills

## **Work Experience**

#### **Product Design Lead**

AsiaYo.com - Taipei City, Taiwan

Apr 2017 - Present

- Develops, implements, and leading the company's design strategy.
- Transform high-level business strategies into a practical action plan.
- Utilizing monitor tools to conduct CRO and user experience optimization.

#### Sr.UI/UX Designer

May 2016 - April 2017

HongKu info Co.,Ltd - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Prioritizing project deliverables and assigning, reviewing, and approving work.
- Creating low/high fidelity prototypes and conducting user testing.
- Effectively develop UI in a clean, well structured, easily maintainable format.

#### **User Experience Design Specialist**

May 2016 - April 2017

SAP - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Served as UX consultant and created high-level wireframe, mockups and prototyping to communicate with related stakeholders.
- Guide and influence User-Centered Design Thinking methods and working process into diversity departments.
- Experienced in diverse projects(insurance, medical) and overcome technical issues.

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Department of Merchant Marine National Taiwan Ocean University - Keelung City, Taiwan

### **Technical skills**

Research, Information Architecture, Wireframing, Mockups, Prototyping, Team Management, Conversion Optimization, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript